welcome to manolife online
tap into a world where every day is
better
enjoy a hassle-free way of updating your
contact details with manulite online
Step One log into your Manulife online
account
tap the menu button
profile
and then tap my profile
Step 2 tap the three dots menu
then tap change contact number
update your contact information by
entering your new mobile or landline
number
[Music]
once done tap next button
step 3 review your details then tap
submit
you will receive a notification once the
changes have been applied
[Music]
experience convenience right at your
fingertips with manulite online
[Music]